The first species to generate a lot of interesting information was frogs.
第一个带来很多有趣信息的物种是青蛙。
And there was a clear pattern here - they proliferate where there is suitable water.
这里有一个清晰的模式，它们在适合的水域繁殖。
Garden ponds are on the increase,rural ponds are disappearing,leading to massive migration to the towns.
花园池塘在增加，乡村的池塘在减少，这导致往城镇的大规模迁徙。
Hedgehogs are also finding it easier to live in urban areas
刺猬也更容易在城市生活，
this time because their predators are not finding it quite so attractive to leave their rural environment, so hedgehogs have a better survival rate in cities.
因为它们的天敌不愿意离开乡村的环境，所以刺猬在城市的存活率更大。
We had lots of sightings, so all in all we had no difficulties with our efforts to count their numbers precisely.
我们有过很多次观察，所以我们在精确的计数上没有问题。
Our final species is the finest of bird singers,the song thrush.
我们最后一个物种是最好的鸟类歌手，画眉。
On the decline in the countryside,they are experiencing a resurgence in urban gardens
它们在城市的花园里再现，在乡村的数目减少了，
because these dadys gardeners are buying lots of different plants
因为现在的园丁买了许多不同的植物，
which means there's an extensive range of seeds around,which is what they feed on.
这意味着有很多种类的种子供它们食用。
Another factor is the provision of nesting places - which is actually better in gardens than the countryside.
另一个因素是花园的筑巢地点比乡村好得多。
Hard to believe it,but it's true.
难以相信，却是真的。
Incidentally, we discovered that a massive new survey on song thrushes is about to be launched,so you should keep an eye open for that.
顺便说一下，我们有大量关于画眉的新发现将会推出，所以你要密切关注。
Now,I'd be happy to answer any questions you may have...
现在，我很乐意回答问题……